Guide to the Derrick A. Bell, Jr. Papers MC.138
New York University Archives
- SERIES II: SPEECHES AND WRITINGS (Accession 95-015)
  - Harvard Blackletter Journal, reprint of edition (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Harvard Blackletter Journal, reprint of edition (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Harvard Law Review Foreward, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Minnesota Law School, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - NCBL Bicentenial Program, 1986-1987 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Northeastern Law School, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - NOVA Law Review, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Ohio Law School, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Pace Law School, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - Puget Sound Law School, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 15)
  - Legal Theory Workshop, 1986-1987 (Box 141, Folder 16)
  - SALT Conference NYC, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 17)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 18)
  - U of O (actually OSU), 1987 (Box 141, Folder 19)
  - Smithsonian Institute 1986 Symposium (Box 141, Folder 20)
  - Tulane Law School, 1986-1987 (Box 141, Folder 21)
  - Harvard-Radcliffe Black Students Association, 1989 (Box 141, Folder 22)
  - Georgia State - Atlanta, 1988 (Box 141, Folder 23)
  - Grace Church Pgh., 1988 (Box 141, Folder 24)
  - Ohio State University, 1988 (Box 141, Folder 25)
  - U of Tennessee, 1988 (Box 141, Folder 26)
  - College of Wooster, 1989 (Box 141, Folder 27)
  - Florida, Jacksonville University, 1989 (Box 141, Folder 28)
  - Employment Research and Policy Prog. CUNY Ms. Sheila Collins, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 29)
  - Rutgers Law School Newark, 1989 (Box 141, Folder 30)
  - Columbia Law School, 1989 (Box 141, Folder 31)
  - Central Connecticut State University, 1989 (Box 141, Folder 32)
  - NC State Raleigh, 1989 (Box 141, Folder 33)
  - Beaumont Texas Al Price, 1989 (Box 141, Folder 34)
  - Institute for Legal Studies - University of Wisconsin Madison - Prof. Linda Greene, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 35)
  - USC - Loring Leadership Lecture, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 36)
  - University of West Virginia, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 37)
  - Seattle Bar Univ. of Washington - Dean Wallace D. Loh, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 38)
  - Tom Paine Award - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 39)
  - Oklahoma Scholarship Leadership Enrichment Program (SLEP), 1988 (Box 141, Folder 40)
  - Northern California ACLU, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 41)
  - Akron Ohio Reading Group, 1991 (Box 141, Folder 42)
  - Stanford and Berkeley, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 43)
  - Wooster College, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 44)
  - Forest Service Portland Oregon, 1988 (Box 141, Folder 45)
  - Community Change, 1987-1988 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262520
  - Detroit, 1987-1989 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Washington D.C. Nightwatch Georgetown, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - California State and San Bernadino, 1990-1991 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Stetson Law School, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - U of Colorado, 1990-1991 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Vermont Law School Tuesday March 26, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Spelman College, 1987-1991 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Occidental Public Affairs Conference - Los Angeles, CA. Ms. Jennifer M. Roth, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Duke University, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Detroit Lawyers, 1990-1991 (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Ohio University, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Yale Journal of Law and Liberation, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Educational Leadership, 1983-1984 (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - Speeches on Disk, 1981-1990 (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - Legal Action Center for the Homeless, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - NYU Judicial AdministrationConference - luncheon speech, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 17)
  - St. James Presbyterian Church St. Nicholas at 141st St., 1992-1994 (Box 142, Folder 18)
  - Boston - National Lawyers Guild, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 19)
  - Rayford Logan Lecture Howard Univ., 1994 (Box 142, Folder 20)
  - NYU Law Review Marshall Tribute, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 21)
  - NYU Alumni Dinners, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - U. Mass Dartmouth, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Scholar-in-Residence 1993-94 Spelman College, 1993-1994 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Clark Atlanta, 1993-1994 (Box 142, Folder 25)
  - Essence Lani Guinier Discussions, 1993-1994 (Box 142, Folder 26)
  - St. Paul's Church with Will Nelson, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 27)
  - National Black MBA, 1992-1994 (Box 142, Folder 28)
  - Howard Alumni of NY, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 29)
  - Black Writers, 1993-1994 (Box 142, Folder 30)
  - Univ. of South Florida, 1993-1994 (Box 142, Folder 31)
  - Feb. 14, 1994 Webster University St. Louis, Missouri (Box 142, Folder 32)
  - University of Illinois at Chicago, 1993-1994 (Box 142, Folder 33)
  - U. of Michigan, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 34)
  - Miami, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 35)
  - NABSE Conf. Houston, Texas, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 36)
  - Univ. of Houston, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 37)
  - Brooklyn College, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 38)
  - West Chester State University, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 39)
  - Univ. Pittsburgh, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 40)
  - Bernadette Devlin, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 41)
  - Department of Agriculture, 1992-1994 (Box 142, Folder 42)
  - Metro Black Bar Association, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 43)
  - Vanderbilt Univ. Nashville, Tenn., 1993 (Box 142, Folder 44)
  - N.Y.Book Fair for Homeless, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 45)
  - NCBL Conference Chicago, IL, 1992-1993 (Box 142, Folder 46)
  - National Council of Churches USA, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 47)
  - Sponsers Eugene. OR, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 48)
  - Washington D.C. Urban League, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 49)
  - Barnes & Noble, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 50)
  - Martha's Vineyard C/R Conference, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 51)
  - NBA Annual Meeting Boca Raton, FL, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 52)
  - Portland Urban League, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 53)
  - ABA Minorities Women, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 54)
  - Equality, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 55)
  - Arizona Bar, 1992-1993 (Box 142, Folder 56)
  - Comm. To Elect Martha James, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 57)
  - Natl. Assoc. of Black Journalists Newport, RI, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 58)
  - U. Pittsburgh Law School Commencement, 1994 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262488
  - African-Am. Employees Assn., 1994 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - UCLA Law Commencement, 1994 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Berkeley Black Graduation, 1992-1994 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - University of Oregon: May 15th, 1994 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Race Matters Conference Princeton, NJ, 1994 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Harvard Medical School, 1994 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Medgar Evers College, 1993-1994 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - NAACP Pittsburgh - April 11th, 1994 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - AALS - Constitutional Law Conference, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Chicago Legal Assist. Fund, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Boston, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Bates College, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - NYU Black/Latino Awards Ceremony, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - NYU Reunion, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Santa Clara Law School, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Chronicle of the Twenty-Seventh Year: Reconsideration, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - John Marshall Law School, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Dominguez Hills, CA, 1991-1993 (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - Middlebury College, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 20)
  - Wesleyan College Afro Studies, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 21)
  - Univ. of Chicago, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 22)
  - Memphis State, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 23)
  - All-Souls Unitarian Church, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 24)
  - Justice Thurgood Marshall Memorial Tribute March 23, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 25)
  - Jamaica, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 26)
  - Caribbean Cultural Center, 1990-1993 (Box 143, Folder 27)
  - John Jay College, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 28)
  - Baruch College, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 29)
  - Smithsonian, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 30)
  - Georgia State, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 31)
  - Puget Sound Law School, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 32)
  - Fordham Law School, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 33)
  - Fourth Annual Conference Law Symposium / Drake Univ. Feb. 12 & 13, 1992, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 34)
  - Harlem Public Library, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 35)
  - Delta Sigma Theta, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 36)
  - Pratt Institute, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 37)
  - African-Am. Read-In, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 38)
  - SMU-Dallas, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 39)
  - Capital Univ. Columbus, OH, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 40)
  - Phil Donahue Show, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 41)
  - NY Law School, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 42)
  - Anti-Bias Comm. MLK Birthday, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 43)
  - AALS, 1990-1993 (Box 143, Folder 44)
  - Schomburg Book Party, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 45)
  - Vassar, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 46)
  - 1st Presby. Church - Brooklyn Paul Smith - Minister, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 47)
  - Denver Forum, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 48)
  - Comm. Service Society of NY, 1990-1992 (Box 143, Folder 49)
  - AALS, 1991-1993 (Box 143, Folder 50)
  - PILF, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 51)
  - San Diego Black Lawyers Dinner, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 52)
  - San Francisco, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 53)
  - Los Angeles, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 54)
  - NY Times Magazine, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 55)
  - Bob Carter Dinner, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 56)
  - Joe Washington, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 57)
  - Natl. Women's Pol. Caucus - Good Guy Award, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 58)
  - Price Public Affairs Forum "Race and Justice in America" Oct. 16, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 59)
  - Women Aloud, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 60)
  - Coalition of 100 Black Women, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 61)
  - Washington State Bar, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262348
  - D.C. Law School, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Portland, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Eugene, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Bridging Communities A Conversation with Rev. Al Sharpton Sept. 10, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Pittsburgh / West VA, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Natl. Lawyer's Guild, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - ABA, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - July '92, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Cambridge, undated (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Schomburg Center Summer Theater Institute, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - NOBO, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Manhattan Outreach - Graduation, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - 1992 Candace Awards/Natl. Coal. Of Black Women, Inc. June 22, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - 4th Ann. Workshop on Critical Race theory 5/31 to 6/4, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - Writings -essays - poems, 1951-1972 (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - Still Looking for the Pony, 1974-1978 (Box 144, Folder 17)
  - The Tonic: An Allegory on Race in America, 1965-1978 (Box 144, Folder 18)
  - Dependent Status, undated (Box 144, Folder 19)
  - Writings, 1991 (Box 144, Folder 20)
  - NYU Law School Articles, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 21)
  - Recent and General, 1982-1991 (Box 144, Folder 22)
  - Publications (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 144, Folder 23)
  - Publications (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 144, Folder 23)
  - Publications (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 144, Folder 24)
  - Publications (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 144, Folder 24)
  - 1989 Sarasohn Lecture (Box 144, Folder 25)
  - Gomes Sermons, 1988-1991 (Box 144, Folder 26)
  - Chicago, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 27)
  - North Carolina Central Law Journal, 1991-1992 (Box 144, Folder 28)
  - Writings-Sources and Responses, 1986-1991 (Box 144, Folder 29)
  - "Confronting Authority" manuscript, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 30)
  - "Confronting Authority" proofs, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 31)
- SERIES III: SUBJECT FILES (Accession 95-015)
  - News Clippings Copies April - May, 1990 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262306
  - Status of Affirmative Action, File Report Harvard, undated (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Statement April 24, 1990 Harvard (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Noble Lectures Harvard December 1990 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Notes and Memoranda May 15, 1991 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Articles by Others re: Affirmative Action, 1990 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Housing, 1980-1989 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Derrick A Bell, Job Opportunities, 1985 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Lawrence, Charles-"The Id, Ego & Equal Protection", 1987 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Thurgood Marshall, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Sheila McIntyre, 1986-1987 (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - Melhourne, Edwin, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Martha Minow Talk, undated (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - Nagae, Peggy, 1986 (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - National Constitution Center, 1986-1987 (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - National Constitution Center, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - New Birth Corporation, 1986-1987 (Box 145, Folder 17)
  - NY Public Library, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 18)
  - Schomburg Bicentennial Exhibition, 1985-1986 (Box 145, Folder 29)
  - Schomburg Bicentennial, 1986-1987 (Box 145, Folder 20)
  - "Say Brother", 1987 (Box 145, Folder 21)
  - Simple Justice File, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 22)
  - Job Referrals File, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 23)
  - Job Referrals File, 1989 (Box 145, Folder 24)
  - Michael Olivas, 1986 (Box 145, Folder 25)
  - Stanford Scandal, 1986-1987 (Box 145, Folder 26)
  - Stanford Law School Scandal, 1985-1986 (Box 145, Folder 27)
  - Thurman Educational Trust, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 28)
  - Thurman Trust, 1986 (Box 145, Folder 29)
  - Howard Thurman Trust, 1985-1986 (Box 145, Folder 30)
  - Williams, Patricia, 1983-1985 (Box 145, Folder 31)
  - Willie, Charles - Controlled Choice Assignment Plan - Bell Comments on, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 32)
  - David Fine File, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 33)
  - Stanford Syndrome, 1985-1986 (Box 145, Folder 34)
  - Stanford Law School, 1986-1987 (Box 145, Folder 35)
  - Harvard Union of Clerical and Technical Workers, 1988 (Box 145, Folder 36)
  - General File, 1989 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262322
  - General File, 1989 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Greenberg Center for Legal Education, undated (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Black Law Students Association, 1987-1989 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Michael Fultz - A Black Appraisal of Public Schooling, 1988 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Randall Kennedy, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Gallery of Greats, 1988 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - General File, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - General File, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Emerge Magazine, 1988 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Allowance, 1988 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Faculty File Current Issues, 1987-1989 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Memos, 1989 (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - Kagan's View of Social Class, 1988 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - Civil Rights Memorial Text, 1989 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - Civil Rights Research Consortium, 1989 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  - Cleveland Marshall College of Law, undated (Box 146, Folder 15)
  - Dalton, Claire, 1988 (Box 146, Folder 16)
  - Delgado, 1987-1989 (Box 146, Folder 17)
  - Educational Tech. Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 146, Folder 18)
  - D. Bell Expenses and Reimbursment, 1987-1988 (Box 146, Folder 19)
  - Florida State Simon Lectures, 1989 (Box 146, Folder 20)
  - Harvard University Memorial Church, 1989 (Box 146, Folder 21)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1988 (Box 146, Folder 22)
  - NCBL (National Conference of Black Lawyers), 1988 (Box 146, Folder 23)
  - Bell Appreciation Weekend, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 24)
  - Philadelphia, 1986-1987 (Box 146, Folder 25)
  - Petra Foundation - Gail Foster, 1990-1991 (Box 146, Folder 26)
  - Pittsburgh Law School, 1990-1991 (Box 146, Folder 27)
  - The Cosby Show, 1990-1991 (Box 146, Folder 28)
  - General Education and Media Clippings on School Desegregation, 1968-1980 (Box 146, Folder 29)
  - Starobin, Robert, 1968 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262314
  - Tarrytown Conference, 1982-1985 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - "Toward a Darkly Radiant Vision of America's Truth" Vincent Harding, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - General Info File, 1971-1980 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Info, 1987-1988 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - NYU, 1991-1992 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies, 1992 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Racism and New Segregation Report, 1992 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Reproductive Rights Update, 1992 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - "Negotiating South Africa's Future", undated (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - "Free Speech in an Open Society", 1992 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - "Berkeley Women's Law Journal", 1989-1992 (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - Univ. of Minnesota Press, 1992 (Box 147, Folder 13)
  - Federal Courts Articles, 1987-1989 (Box 147, Folder 14)
  - Law Articles and Pamphlets 1, 1970-1988 (Box 147, Folder 15)
  - Law Articles and Pamphlets 2, 1989-1990 (Box 147, Folder 16)
  - Law Articles and Pamphlets 3, 1990-1992 (Box 147, Folder 17)
  - Computer Instructions, undated (Box 147, Folder 18)
  - Public Interest Job Search Guide, 1990 (Box 147, Folder 19)
  - Appellant's Brief - Child Abuse, 1988 (Box 147, Folder 20)
  - "The Negro Family", 1965 (Box 147, Folder 21)
  - The Scribes Journal of Legal Writing, 1991 (Box 147, Folder 22)
  - The Responsive Community, 1991-1992 (Box 147, Folder 23)
  - Overcrowded Times, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 24)
  - Reading Improvement Exercises, 1956 (Box 147, Folder 25)
  - The American Journal of Legal History, vol. 32, 1988 (Box 147, Folder 26)
  - The American Journal of Legal History, vol. 33, 1989 (Box 147, Folder 27)
  - The American Journal of Legal History, vol. 33, 1989 (Box 147, Folder 28)
  - Visions of the First Amendment for a New Millenium, 1992 (Box 147, Folder 29)
  - The American University Journal of International Law and Policy, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 30)
  - Cardozo Law Review, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 31)
  - Journal of Legal Education, 1989 (Box 147, Folder 32)
  - The Modern Supreme Court, 1972 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262330
  - "The Black Scholar", 1987-1990 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - "Constitution", 1989-1992 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Law Pamphlets, 1988-1990 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - American Bar Foundation Research Journal, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - NOVA Law Review, 1988-1991 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Journals and Magazines, 1988-1991 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Minority and Justice Task Force Final Report, 1990 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Modern Constitutional Theory: A Reader, 1991 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Directory of Law Teachers, 1989-1990 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Harvard Blackletter Journal, 1990 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Harvard Journal of Law & Public Society, 1991 (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Harvard Journal on Legislation, 1991 (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - Harvard Law Review, 1989 (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - Harvard Law Review, 1989 (Box 148, Folder 15)
  - Harvard Law Review, 1991 (Box 148, Folder 16)
  - Who Will Teach?, 1991 (Box 148, Folder 17)
  - Children and Family, 1980-1991 (Box 148, Folder 18)
  - Interracial Sex, Men, 1981-1991 (Box 148, Folder 19)
  - Women, 1984-1991 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262298
  - Indians, 1974-1991 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Comparative Racism, 1988-1991 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Homosexuality, 1988-1991 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Law Articles and Pamphlets 1, 1986-1990 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Law Articles and Pamphlets 2, 1987-1991 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Criminal Justice System and Race, 1983-1991 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Papers and Articles A-D, 1973-1991 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Papers and Articles F-W, 1973-1991 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262512
  - Law Articles and Pamphlets, 1989-1991 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Connection, 1990-1991 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Educational Committees, Joint, Toussaint, Thurman, 1991 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Info on Education, 1983-1991 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Diversity in Legal Education A-C, 1985-1991 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Diversity in Legal Education F-W, 1985-1991 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Ames Court Panel, 1989 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Law Journals, 1988-1991 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Info / Law Education, 1986-1990 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - SALT, 1990-1991 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Articles, 1976-1991 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Civil Rights, 1986-1991 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - Civil Rights, 1986-1991 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262504
  - Civil Rights, 1986-1991 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Housing A-G, 1987-1990 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Housing H-S, 1987-1990 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Misc Info. Housing, 1987-1991 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Journals, 1987-1991 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Journals, 1987-1991 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action, 1986-1991 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action Misc. Info, 1986-1990 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action Journals, 1986-1990 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Black Faculty Report Materials, 1987-1989 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Minority Voting Rights, 1987-1990 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - San Francisco, Eugene, 1993-1994 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262447
  - Dog Records, 1968-1978 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Martha's Vineyard Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Welcome to Oregon, undated (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - A.J. Lewis, 1962-1965 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Georgia State Plaque, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Linz Audain, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Harlem Events, 1991-1992 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - NYU Law School, 1991-1993 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Articles and Papers, 1989-1992 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Rick Tejada-Flores, 1992 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Toward a Black Legal Scholarship - Culp, undated (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - SALT, 1992-1993 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Dewart, J, 1991 (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Black Films - Amos 'n'Andy, 1977-1991 (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - Publications, 1990-1992 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262405
  - Notes, 1989-1991 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Toussaint Institute, 1990-1991 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Intimate Differences, 1991 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - CRLA, 1992 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Harvard Resignation, 1992 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - PDC, 1989-1991 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Simple Justice File, 1991 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - HLS - Diversity Suit, 1992 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action, 1988 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Public Advocates 20th Anniversary, 1991-1994 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Travel Expenses, 1990-1994 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Derrick III - Case RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Laing, 1991 (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Publications, 1991-1994 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - Misc., 1988-1992 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Bell Plans 91-92, 1991-1992 (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - Clark Foundation, 1991 (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - AALS, 1991 (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - Harvard Law School, 1991-1992 (Box 153, Folder 20)
  - NYU Law School, 1991-1992 (Box 153, Folder 21)
  - SALT, 1991 (Box 153, Folder 22)
  - NARAL, 1991 (Box 153, Folder 23)
  - Legal Resource Center, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262421
  - Publications and Speeches, 1984-1992 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Notes, Pictures, 1991-1992 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Affirmative Action DeVine Gift Chronicle, 1980-1987 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - DeKalb County Segregation Case, 1990 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Whitney M. Young Service Awards Reception, 1992 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Harvard Law School, 1991-1992 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - AFRAM, 1989-1992 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - SALT, 1991-1993 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - NYU Law School, 1990-1992 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Lecture Papers - not by Bell, 1992 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Frank L. Natter Manuscript, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - "The Double Minority" by Deborah Merritt, 1992 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, Notes, Pictures, 1988-1992 (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - Committee Against Anti-Asian Violence, 1992 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - Boycott Miami, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - Publications, 1987-1991 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - Publications, 1992 (Box 154, Folder 19)
  - Stephen M. Feldman Manuscripts, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 20)
  - NYU Law School, 1992-1994 (Box 154, Folder 21)
  - Riots, Race and Social Reform, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042262397
  - Peter Yu, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Notes, Pictures, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Remarriage RESTRICTED, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 4)